I am a graphic designer based in New York. I specialize in typography, branding, website design, and photography. With a keen eye for detail and a passion for creating visually compelling experiences, I bring creativity and innovation to every project.

Education

Parsons School of Design (BFA)

2020 - 24

Major: Communication Design (STEM program)

Minor: Photography Honours: Dean's list

Skills Typography

> Branding Sketching Editorial Motion Graphic Photography **Book Production**

Coding

Language Procifiency

Native in Mandarin, Proficient in English.

Software and Visualization

**Adobe Creative Suite** 

including InDesign, Photoshop, Illustrator, Premiere, After Effect, and Lightroom

**Photography** 

DSLRs, digital cinema cameras and accessories, lighting for portrait photoshooting, and analog photography.

**Website Coding Languages** 

HTML, CSS and Javascript

**Figma** 

Typetool 3

**Microsoft Suits** 

Experience

Li Tang Community, Creative Intern

October 2024-present New York, US

**Graphic Design** 

Poster design of UAAD Art Festival JUKEBOX OF DISSONANCE.

(October 2024)

Led reorganization and redesign of the Li Tang Community website to enhance readability

(November 2024-present)

PUFF N' POOF, Designer

October 2024-present New York, US

**Product Design** 

Created brand identity for a

line of party merchandise. (October 2024-present)

**Graphic Design** 

Developed brand identity for

the new label Ing.Room.

(November 2024-present)

Office of Luke Bulman, Designer June 2024-October 2024

New York, US

**Editorial Design** 

Volume 6 & 7 of the book series Bioclimatic Ceramic Assemblies for the Architectural Ceramic Assemblies Workshop (ACAW).

(June 2024-October 2024)

Media Matters in Landscape Architecture, a book edited by Karen M'Closkey and Keith VanDerSys.

(August 2024-October 2024)

Cover Design

Cover design for Form and Fortification: The Art of Military Architecture in Renaissance Italy, Book by Morgan Ng.

(July 2024)

Cover Design for Media Matters in Landscape Architecture.

(Sept 2024)

NOON Studio, Internship Oct 2023-Dec 2023

New York, US

**Branding** 

Led the concept design and fabrication of Gables Baldwin Park's identity.

(Oct 2023)

Video Design

Developed seasonal video wall concepts for Zero Irving.

(Nov 2023)

Packaging Design & Branding

Designed New Year merchandise and e-blasts for NOON studio. enhancing brand visibility and engagement with target audiences.

(Nov 2023-Dec 2023)